Guide to the Theatre collection, 1937-1967
Department of Special Collections
Theatre collection,
1937-1967
Special Collections M0201
N/A
.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Various sources
Scope and Content
Playscripts by Philip Dunning, correspondence to and from Dunning, and a script by Morton Grant.
Container List
- Dunning, Philip: all TLS from Dunning to Sam Stark (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1. n.d.
  - 2. [ca. 1966 Nov. 6]
  - 3. 1966, Dec. 7
  - 4. 1967, Jan. 3with two snapshots re: Dunning's farm
  - 5. 1967, July 19with two snapsots re: Dunning's studio
  - 6. 1967, June 20
  - 7. 1967 Sept. 1with snapshot of Dunning's land in Connecticut
  - 8. 1967, Oct. 17
  - 9. 1967, Nov. 26with enclosed letter: TSL from Rube Goldberg to Philip Dunning
  - 10. n.d.
  - 11. 1968, Jan. 30
  - 12. 1968 Feb. 23
  - 13. 1968, April 17
  - 14. 1968 Oct. 26ALS Jack Aranson [?] to Sam Stark re: Dunning's "Jack Ruby" play
- Dunning, Philip (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 15. 1931 Jan. 1Pamphlet on "The Coffee House" Club, of which Dunning was a member
  - 16. 1967 Aug."Sequel to a Verdict" published copy of play by Dunning, 1961. Has inscription by Dunning to Sam Stark.
- Dunning, Philip (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 17. 1967 Aug."A Fantastic Chain of Events" by Philip Dunning. - in 3 acts. Typescript and memeographed with photo. 1965. -revised 1966 and 1967. Copy sent to Sam STark with inscription Aug. 1967 and TSL to Stark from Dunning n.d. re: new play ending
  - 18. 1967 Oct."A Fantastic Chain of Events" or "Jack Ruby Tells All!"- by Dunning. One Act - revised edition of # 17 above. Typescript and mimeo. 1965, revised 1967. Copy sent to Sam Stark with inscription, October, 1967. (Photo)
- Grant, Morton (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1. 1937, May"Inside Story" or "Love in the Air", revised final script - typed and mimeo. Screen play by Morton Grant. Original Story by Roy Chanslor. (Ronald Reagan's first movie)